The day I proposed to you
you asked me to be honest with you always, didn't you?
You said that you are and that you will always be.
From that day to today
I lied to you a lot because I didn't want to hurt your feelings.
My sister is getting a divorce.
Sang Jin came to my house because of that.
I was going to tell you but I didn't find the right time.
I also hid and lied about many things.
I get why you misunderstand the situation about me and Dong Bi.
I understand how you felt when I didn't
answer your call and stayed with Sang Jin.
Dong Bi is my friend but she's also your friend.
I met her before I met you.
Dong Bi dated Ki Joong because I introduced her to him.
Whenever Dong Bi went through
difficult times dating Ki Joong,
I felt sorry because I thought I had caused the problem.
I also felt bad for her.
I thought a man and woman could be friends, as
long as one doesn't have feelings for the other.
All three of us got along very well and you didn't get annoyed by it.
So I thought it wouldn't be a problem. I'm sorry.
Because I thought I shouldn't get jealous.
I was annoyed but I trusted you and her.
When you lied about Sang Jin,
I wanted to create the same situation
so you can feel what I felt.
But I realized how petty I was after
that situation actually came about.
Before I met you, there was a moment
that I thought I loved somebody.
But while I loved you, I felt ashamed of that love.
I wished you were the first man.
Hae Yoon, I'm not Prince Charming.
And I can't be your father.
I want to be respected as a man.
But sometimes I want to be weak and comforted by somebody.
I am sorry.
We all have weakness.
I felt inferior to you while
preparing for the wedding, just like you.
As you know
I am ambitious.
I want my life to be simple.
I just want to love my wife and raise my child.
And I want to enjoy life with a little bit of money.
I thought I could have that life with you.
I thought if I love somebody, I should do whatever she wants.
But now I don't know if that's love.
I think our lives start now.
I thought it was both of our parents who caused the problems while preparing the wedding.
But that was not it.
The problem was you and me.
The problems you and I have were the biggest obstacles.
I don't know who I really am.
I think I'm...
one of the goods made by a social convention.
Jun Sang Jin and Dong Bi might become problems as we live on.
What's important is where our heart goes.
The problems we both can work out is
different than what I can work out.
It's best that I should be alone now.
If we get back together, I wish it happens
because we love each other so much.
Thank you for respecting me.
Let's go now.
We can at least shake our hands, right?
No, I am not going to.
If I do, I might not let you go.
Then don't let it go.
No. Good bye.
Do you open today?
We do. But the menu is limited.
And we will take a while. But I'll refill the menu as much as you want, just today.
Are you getting undressed already?
Do you not want me to?
I haven't seen you in Han Bok in a long time.
But I have to go meet somebody.
- Ah, Hae Yoon's mom?
- Today will be the last time to see her.
Be nice. Don't hurt her feelings.
She hurts my feelings. I don't.
- I'm on time, aren't I?
- Yeah. It will take only two hours.
When can I get Hae Yoon's invitation?
The wedding is soon, isn't it?
She will give it when she think it's the right time.
- Bye.
Hey.
- Am I late?
- I came early.
- What do you want to drink?
- I ordered already.
I ordered what you always drink. It saves us time too.
She's trying to win me, isn't she?
I should've told you this earlier. I canceled the wedding hall.
Now you act so fast.
I asked my son and he said nothing
suspicious happened between him and Dong Bi.
That's not proof. That's just an excuse.
I asked my husband about
that since he met Hae Yoon.
He said it's not because of Dong Bi.
It was my mistake.
There must be a reason why you thought like that.
He said she broke up because she loves him.
What? What the hell are you talking about?
Why would they break up because they love each
other? People break up if they don't.
I think she had an inferiority complex.
Why does my kid have an inferiority complex?
She's pretty and has a nice job.
But you're not.
I know. Why would she have that?
We met and talked because of our kids.
But we didn't have them married.
I wish Hae Yoon can meet a nice man.
I don't know if Jung Hoon can meet a nice woman.
He still can't get over her.
I met him a while ago and he said he
will wait for her. I felt so bad.
He will forget about her as time goes.
There are things that can and cannot be
forgotten as time goes on.
I know these parents who were against their
son's marriage and ruined his life.
Now he's 40 and still not married.
They are so worried that he can't get married.
They regret what they have done to him.
The children's opinions are the most important.
I know that but I think their families are important too.
Of course they are.
If a mother-in-law is so picky about her bottom
drawers, then she's a bad mother-in-law.
A marriage isn't a business.
My family wasn't like that.
I don't know what kind of in-law family she will meet next time.
Parents who have a son is criminal these days.
A long time ago, the husband and wife
live with the husband's family.
So the in-law family took care of them
but these days, they live separately.
Anyways, thank you for everything.
We talked and I got to experience a new culture.
She's sick. What is a new culture?
I also experienced a new culture because of you.
I've never heard the saying parents who have a son are criminals.
She never loses.
Now the relationship between you and my family
is done here. A successful conclusion.
You can't win over your child though.
I'll make Jung Hoon take my side.
Sure. A successful conclusion.
Then good bye. Thank you for everything.
Thank you for not clinging to me.
Sure. Bye.
- Good bye.
An inferiority complex? I don't understand.
What's wrong with Hae Yoon?
What is the true reason?
Now it's finally done. I feel so good.
- Hey.
- Your phone isn't roaming yet.
- I know you know about this.
- Is that really true?
Yeah. She got me at the airport.
Yeah. But how did you know that fast?
I can't even hide my private life.
You tell everybody. Don't make them call me.
How could this happen?
I can't believe that bitch really did that.
Are you not mad?
Are you having a party now?
I can't believe you. You didn't know?
You didn't know this would happen?
Wasn't she suspicious?
She was. She was very suspicious. So I thought she's naturally suspicious.
I'm not letting this go.
Then are you going to tell people that
you're avenging a woman who fooled your son?
All the people know. Even the press knows about this.
I turned my phone off.
Don't avenge her. You look so immature.
Let's just let it go.
How can I let it go?
Do you want to sleep here tonight?
I don't like this house.
If I see the outside from the window, I feel like jumping out the window.
How can you say that in front of your kid?
How can I not? You're the only one who knows everything about me.
- How's Dad?
- He's freaking out more than I am.
Her father's business will suffer.
Your dad said he won't get any products from their company.
- Stop him.
- Find another woman. You should get married.
I'm not listening to you anymore.
- What?
- I did once.
- I don't think I have to do it again.
- What are you talking about?
I think you used all your veto cards.
That's what I thought. But I got one now.
This is so humiliating.
You won't feel as humiliated as I am.
Chae Young is a woman that Dad brought.
He should take the responsibility.
What you should remember is I did get married.
Just like you wanted me to.
I'm getting married to a woman I love.
No way. Who said you can do that?
You know how I am if I decide to do something.
- Nobody can convince me.
- I'm about to decide to do something.
When I changed my mind to be a cook, I
thought that was my last time to decide.
But now the situation is different.
So you and Dad should think about it differently.
I'll do something else for you but not the marriage.
Why? Do you want to have a daughter-in-law
who will have a miserable life like you?
Does misery love company?
Are you going to be best friends with her?
Yeah, you're right. I want to have
somebody that suffers what I suffered.
I forgot that you like to make people's
lives miserable just because yours is.
- You must be tired.
- I'm so tired.
Do you want something to drink?
- You know it, don't you?
- Know what?
The reason why Hae Yoon broke up.
I don't know. How would I?
Then find out. She's a sharp spoon.
Even if she's not confident, she should've said she is.
She's perfect. Why did she say she lost to reality?
She is talking a load of bollocks.
There must be a real reason.
Did you hear something from somebody?
Jung Hoon's mother has no answer.
I usually don't say that but she doesn't have an answer.
She's so immature since she just stays at home after meeting a husband like a Buddha.
She doesn't care about other people.
Hae Yoon thinks I'm the worst?
I think Jung Hoon's mom is worse than I am.
Why do you keep seeing her then?
I'm trying to get them back together.
You don't like Mrs. Ha. Why?
But Mr. Ha is a great man.
Hae Yoon didn't get a father's love.
It'd be nice if she feels a warm love from him.
Mrs. Ha can't do anything if Mr. Ha says something.
But Hae Yoon doesn't want it. We should respect her.
Why doesn't she want it? Jung Hoon said he will wait.
He said there's something Hae Yoon needs to figure out herself.
What is it that you and I don't even know about it?
Hae Yoon will figure it out herself.
So what has she done so far?
All she had to do was walk into the
wedding hall but she canceled it.
Then she's not ready to get married confidently.
Don't say that.
I didn't tell neighbors that Hae Yoon's wedding was called off.
I think Jung Hoon is the right guy for her.
What about Sang Jin?
He's such a sly guy. I don't like him.
Sang Jin is a back up.
But I haven't seen his parents yet. I think Jung Hoon is perfect for her.
She calculated right. Her calculation was right.
So don't say anything about it. Just find out the reason. I'll solve the problem.
Okay.
I should get involved. If I leave it up to you guys, you only waste time.
- What took you so long?
- The maid is taking the day off tomorrow.
So I prepared breakfast for tomorrow.
You didn't have to do that. You're so lovely.
- Sit down.
- I'll take a shower first.
Hey, Aunt.
Really?
I can't believe this.
Are you sure about it?
I feel bad for Ki Joong.
Alright. She's so bad.
Okay. I'll call my sis tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Did something happen to Ki Joong?
I can't believe it.
- How could this happen?
- Did something happen on the honeymoon?
They didn't even go. The bride disappeared at the airport.
She planned it all.
She had a boyfriend but her parents were against it.
So she used Ki Joong.
- Then what's going to happen?
- I don't know.
He must be shocked and so must his parents.
Just pretend you didn't hear about it for a while.
No. She felt sorry for me when Jung
Hoon's marriage was called off.
I should feel sorry for her now.
This is worse than what happened to Jung Hoon.
Marriage causes so many problems to many families.
Where are you going?
I was going to come to you anyway.
- Why?
- This.
What's this?
She gave these when she broke up with me.
She's so weird. I gave them to her as a gift.
Why did she give them back to me?
What should I do with them?
- Then what should I do?
- I don't like her.
You keep them until you get a new girlfriend and then give them to her.
How can I do that?
It was Hae Yoon's once. You're...
Fine. Don't get mad at me.
I want us to be like before.
Before Hae Yoon was involved between us.
Am I dating you or something?
- Why do you keep talking back to me?
- Because you're making me do that.
Fine. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for talking back to you.
Don't be. I know how you feel but
I feel so angry seeing you sad.
Ki Joong's marriage went wrong. I came to tell you this.
You should know it so you don't
make any mistakes like him.
Why did it go wrong? It was a business.
A business can fail.
Not every business goes well.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
Then do it.
- Put me down if you can't.
- I'm going to do it.
Thank you. This is my idea of romance.
If we enter this room, we can finally do it!
Let's go.
Oh my god.
I'm going to do it no matter what.
Are you okay?
I'm not.
- Shit.
- Did you just say shit?
Yeah. You must be in pain.
Come here.
- I'll bring some hot packs.
- Wait.
- I think it's not hurting me anymore.
- You think?
- Then it's not hurting you anymore.
- But it actually hurts.
I'm in pain because of you.
Then I'm the medicine.
Let me give you some treatment.
What do you think?
- The pain is gone.
- Really?
- Look at this.
- It is gone!
- Are you that happy?
- Yeah!
Father...
Why aren't you answering my phone call?
Please stay out of my life.
What's all this?
I don't know. I woke up early.
Don't do that. You must be tired.
Let's just have some bread.
I wanted to do it. It was so romantic.
Making breakfast for someone I love.
Your idea of romance is very practical.
I want to be a good girlfriend. Don't you remember how we met?
How did we meet?
I don't know. How did we meet?
I think I saw you for the first time when you poured water for Ki Joong.
Yeah. That was quite memorable.
A man and a woman are so interesting.
I never imagined us to be like this back then.
That's why a life is worthy to live.
As you live life, unexpected things can happen.
You do everything what others do.
- So you don't like it?
- I like it.
You're so cute.
- Sorry I called you a busy man.
- It was your call. I should come.
I have a goal to reach now. Take this.
I found out you like dolls. So I bought Browny. He's a hit these days.
- Browny?
- Get rid of the teddy bears.
It's not for you.
He's going to control me if he becomes my son-in-law.
- Okay.
- Put him in you room.
Okay.
- Mrs. Jung.
- Yes?
Wouldn't it look good if you put him next to the teddy bears?
Sure. You're so sweet.
He's always butting in my business.
I was happy that you like dolls.
People who like dolls are not bad.
You thought I was bad?
I'm just saying. You're kind of cranky.
Are you going to give me some tea or food?
I asked you to come because I think you might know.
Know what?
What did Hae Yoon say about her break up?
I didn't hear the reason from her but it won't
be just one reason. It's probably complicated.
Why do you ask?
I need to know that. Can you find out?
It can be inferred from all the situations
she had. Do you have to know the reason?
I should know the reason, so as not
to make the same mistake.
We can never be sure that
something like this won't happen again.
What did Hae Yoon say?
She said she lost to herself and reality.
She wasn't confident about the marriage.
What do you think the reason is?
Since she's talking around the subject, the reason is a person.
If she says directly who the person is, that person's feelings get hurt.
So she made up the reasons.
I know. So who is that person?
I think it's you.
Me? Me?
Yeah. Was I too direct?
You're speaking nonsense.
You went too far.
I think it's reasonable.
It was because of her own mother?
What did I do wrong?
No way.
Well. How others think about you is different
than how you think about yourself.
I think you should leave now.
I'm sorry if you're mad.
I thought you were good at this but you aren't.
Then I'll leave now.
Bye.
Hug Browny when you sleep.
He's kind of saucy.
You look saucy too.
What is the real reason? It can't be me.
Is it really a person? Who is the person?
Sis. I'm so sorry.
- Are you happy?
- What?
You felt sorry for me when Jung Hoon's
marriage was canceled. So I came here.
The restaurant is opened. I thought it'd be closed.
This shows people that my son is totally fine with that.
- You're here.
- Yeah. You opened the restaurant.
Yeah. other cooks are taking a day off so I cook today.
I only take reservations.
- Don't work too hard.
- I'm not.
I'll leave you two alone now.
He looks too fine.
He must have suffered a lot.
He gets stronger when the critical situation comes.
That's not true. He's a human and has a heart.
He has to try harder to look fine like that.
- I feel bad.
- What do you know?
We have our own ways to overcome situations like this.
Where's Chae Young?
I don't care where she is. She humiliated
her parents. I bet she won't be happy.
How could she do such things like this? Who is her boyfriend?
You have so many questions.
I'm sorry but I'm so curious.
How's she going to live anyways?
She doesn't need to worry about that at least.
She planned everything.
Her father gave her money when
she got married. She's clever.
I feel bad for her father for having a daughter like her.
I'd never forgive my child if he did the same thing.
I already feel bad for your future daughter-in-law.
I feel bad for your future daughter-in-law.
She's going to have to endure your
self-deluded snobbiness. I'm not like that at least.
I think that's better than horror.
Your family will take a hit because of the disengagement.
But my family won't take a hit
even if he divorces three times.
This is called dignity.
I shouldn't have come here.
If I talk to you for 30 minutes,
I feel like I've talked to you for three hours.
That means I make people concentrate on me when I talk.
You need to get along with your husband.
You're doing this because you want to get attention.
Are you giving me advice?
You came to comfort me? No, you did not.
I must be a comfort to you. My life itself must be comforting to you
Geez, seriously, she's such a drag
How is everything going?
Well for the first 2 years, it will be hard to make ends meet. I don't expect the company to grow so fast
that's a good thinking. Not too vain. That's why I invested in your business
I am thinking of planning a simple wedding and link it with city hall or church
like an event for couples who never had wedding ceremony
I thought you were just focusing on online presence, you're thinking about targeting offline clients as well?
I am toyhinking about mixing the two.
Have you heard? Chaeyong. She married Gong Kijoon
I didn't tell you since you knew Chairman Gong's son
Even though she doesn't look it, Chaeyong has a complicated dating life.
[wicked patriarch]
I have to answer this call
Where are you
-Is this your office?
-what would you like to drink?
no need
can you even work here? It's size of a shoebox
what do you want to say exactly?
I asked you to look over some stuff
Why would I review that?
Would you like me to kill that punk? If you want me to, I will. I will find a way
He hurt you. If someone hurts you, you need to chase him to the ends of the earth
that's my child
I don't know why you show up all of a sudden, talking about your child and all
I most certainly cut all ties with you, father
Can you cut ties just because you say so?
no. I changed my last name, left your household, and tried all I can to live a different life from you. But the persistent gene inside me went and found a guy exactly like you
I thought if I could earn that guy's love, I will be repaid for all the love that I couldn't get from you, father
If you want to stab him, stab yourself first
who hurt whom?
that's why I don't deal with girls
It's enough I gave birth to you and here you talk about love nonsense. That's why it just doesn't work with girls
How did Jungdo leave this world? Whose fault was it?
Don't bring his name up. He's not my son
If he was my son, he wouldn't have been such a weakling
When he was seven years old, I dragged Jungdo to a mountain in the middle of the night because I wanted to kill him
No matter how hard I try, I couldn't become a boy
I thought you would pay attention to me if he was gone
I have to keep Jungdo buried in my heart for the rest of my life.
Do you know how painful that is?
I have absolutely no fantasies about you, father
What happened to Jungdo? The one you loved so much
I don't need your love.
You could become an actor. I have heard enough of your nonsense. Come back to the company now.
The company doesn't have any talented people?
The fact that you are my bloodline, that puts you above anyone else
There are still companies that run under such old fashioned way?
That means the company will fail. I'm not going into a company that has no vision.
You're being very arrogant. I understand that you changed after leaving the family and going through hard times.
But did somebody tell you to leave?
The world is my family. My older sisters didn't give me a single call.
Even if I left home, they were afraid if you found out that they keep in touch, you will cut off any financial support. They were afraid to lose their inheritance
Is that family? Tell me truthfully. You are trying to use me as a shuttle, right?
Your second wife's son is seven years old, right?
Until he has grown... until he can take over the company...
Are you shocked since I saw through you?
- Pathetic girl.
- You can never win me.
Time is on my side.
When my time comes, you will have no choice but to stand behind me.
Your wealth! if you die, I have my share in it
I just have to wait. Stop trying to do something with me for money.
It's a shame. Why were you born as a girl?
With your gut and spirit, why couldn't you have been a boy?
I am going to try to understand you because you are a pitiful person.
If you have money lying around, invest in me.
Don't waste your time doing background checks.
I know this makes no sense, but I'm telling you since you do things that don't make sense.
Don't touch that man.
Love or work, I am going to take care of it with my own hands.
Please leave now.
What are you doing here?
There is no reason to see each other. I give you back the bracelet
You have become so much more attractive
than when I dated you.
Why is that?
I guess it's because I didn't love you.
I think so too. I feel competitive to win you back. Let's date again.
Why are you being like this? It hasn't been a long time since I called off the engagement.
When I heard that you are no longer with that guy, I decided to do this.
I am mourning for my love that didn't work out
please don't bother me.
Why you do that?
Why are you courting me all of a sudden?
The Jung Sang Jin that left me for a law firm daughter.
That is the real you.
People can make mistakes and they learn the lesson from it.
I am a smart guy. Like you said, I am not doing it just out of pure emotions.
You are the ideal woman for marriage.
I like how after you choose a man you focus solely on him.
After marriage, I might have to live with a woman for 70 years. I need a woman who is hard as cement.
In order to become cement, you need water, but you don't have any.
Well, let's end it there. Let's go out and grab a bit. Stop playing hard to get. If you continue, you might bounce away
I will bounce away. I am gonna go home early
I met your mother at your home. Aren't your curious?
-Shall we have company dinner tonight?
-I have prior engagement
-what prior engagement?
-is it with Mr(s) Scary?
-yes
-who is this Mr(s) Scary exactly? I am dying to find out
I must know the reason. What the real reason you guys broke up?
It's between the two of us. Mother
You didn't say that last time. You said it's the problems Hae Yoon needs to solve by herself.
Then what is it? Is it me? Is it because of me?
Why do you think that way?
I asked Lawyer Jung and he said it might be because of me.
How could that be? Why would Hye Yoon say we should break up because of you?
That's why I thought. I can't get along with Sang Jin.
He bought this weird doll, but I like yours better.
Don't worry about it too much.
She and I are separated from each other but we still make the right decision.
What do you mean by a smart decision? Are you saying it is alright if you two break up?
Anything can happen.
You are saying it would be alright to break up.
Give us some time.
You are thinking too much. You are young!
You might lose a lot of things because of that.
Do you think you will be young forever? You can handle her problems
If somebody is stuck, the person next to her helps her fix it.
Why can't you do that? Do you want her to marry Sang Jin?
Why do you want to know so badly why we broke up?
My daughter has a problem getting married. I can't just sit here and do nothing.
I should help her.If I were you, I'd help her solve her problems.
How can I solve you?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Do you like me?
I'm too shy to tell you that.
He knows something for sure, but isn't saying it. What could it be?
Alright. I met your mother and she said she cancelled the booking for the wedding hall.
Yes.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Don't think too long. I haven't seen a person who thinks for a long time and not make the wrong decision.
- Drink.
- Don't give me another. I will just have one glass
don't be like that. Have some more and say "Give me more, Give me more" couple more times. It's addictive, I would like to hear it more
-It's kind of odd
-What is?
I certainly loved you at one point, and you were everything to me once
how can my feelings disappear without leaving a trace?
You're killing the mood again. What's so great about Ha Jung Woon?
-What does he have other than being tall?
-to-cute (totally cute)
-what is "to-cute"?
-look it up on the web.
he's a "to-cute, to-cute" guy
After some time passes, will my feelings toward Junghoon become a bit numb like the way I feel when I see you now?
I am sure he's no different. Someone as seductive as me is being treated like any old man.
-Let's get going
-Drink some more. You're attractive when you drink.
I am already so attractive that you are losing your head. If I become any more attractive, what will happen to you?
Oppa, don't be nice to me. I'm not going out with you.
You're not going to Jung Hoon either.
Yes, I won't go to him either.
The reason why you two broke up is because of your mother.
Even if you don't tell me, I could see through you.
Give it a serious thought. It's not easy to meet a guy like me.
You don't marry based on emotions but based on rationale.
I could cover your mother. I could make suggestions to solve the problems you have.
This is the conclusion I have reached based on the analyzing the relationship between you and me. Marriage.
No matter what you do, you're just pathetic.
She's above average for sure. I am usually able to win them over by now. But I am not able to win her over.
I really can't figure it out.
I AM SO EMBARRASSED! You embarrass me. To show you to other people, it's embarrassing!
It couldn't be. No. No way. It wasn't me.
I think it's you.
Why are you sitting there like a statute?
I was just sitting still.
-Why did you meet Sanjin?
-He told you about that already?
He's quite a blabbermouth.
If you're thinking about pairing him with me, don't even try it.
Why not try? He's quite a catch. It seems like he really likes you.
It's best for a woman to marry a man who chases after her. It's easier that way.
Tomorrow is the day for home visit inspection for the older sister.
-Look at you changing the subject
-Let's sleep over at Hyejin's place tomorrow.
How did you two meet?
I ran a clinic together with my ex-wife whom I met at college. She was a nurse's aide at the clinic.
I was married to my ex-wife. I met my ex-wife at college and we had similar financial background and intellect.
I was preparing myself for college entrance exam while working. So I often studied at the clinic.
He was the director then and he thought highly of me trying to go to college and often buy me yummy food and give me a ride home.
I didn't see him as a man because he was the Director of the clinic, married and much older than me.
If you hadn't really liked me, when I offered to buy you a meal, you wouldn't have obliged.
She try to seduce from the beginning.
He's trying to provoke so I will get worked up.
Previously, he made me out to be a homewrecker in front of you.
You're a homewrecker! I didn't falsify who you are.
If I am a homewrecker, what does that make you? You cheated on your wife.
Do you have something to say? Both of you, please calm down.
What is the reason for failure of your marriage? Plaintiff Nam Do Hyun?
She switches out furniture every year. She buys plate sets that cost $10,000
No matter how much money I make, I can I handle all that?
Do you know how many luxury purses she owns?
I don't own a single luxury purse. I sold them all because you didn't give me living expenses.
Do you think I bought high end bags and plates because that's what I wished?
I bought them to fit your standard.
You were happy when I served guests with them.
Why are you now saying otherwise?
Have you stopped giving her money for living expenses?
These days, I don't even have money to run a clinic.
Of course I had to cut down on living expenses.
You didn't cut down, you didn't give me any.
If I don't give you money, you could earn money to make a living.
Who will take care of Taewon? You don't care about our child?
Both parties, please hold back on the emotions and only answer the questions asked.
We have to say our farewells now.
But you will live on in my heart.
He cheated on me the entire time he was married.
As you could see from the audio recording submitted as evidence. he admitted to it.
That's not valid. She recorded it after manipulating me to answering in a way that will be to her advantage.
Who could come up with "there is a beast living inside me"?
That's your usual thought.
Defendant Jung Hyejin. Why did you decide to get a divorce?
The woman he was cheating with came to see me and asked me to step away.
She's a racing model and her contact was saved as "Mechanic" on his cell phone.
They had been together for 3 years.
Before they were just flings. But it was different this time around.
You were treated the same way how you treated his ex-wife.
It's karma.
As a price for the wrongs I have committed, I lived with him,
I think I paid the price.
I am not in a relationship with the racing model.
She has misunderstood.
How did you get to know this racing model?
She was a patient of mine. I fixed many parts of her face.
Since she came to my clinic quite a few times, I hung out with her couple times
I slept with her but it was nothing serious. She has misunderstood.
You're still with her now.
You're quite shameless.
I didn't want to get a divorce so I even begged for her forgiveness.
But her mother made a scene at my clinic. Thus, I decided to get a divorce.
After that incident, the reputation of my clinic has gone down and affected the clinic's revenue.
Please provide proof of declining revenue as an evidence. My mom just removed couple things on the desk in front of the clinic employee and that will have an effect on the sales?
Your mother interfered in our marriage the whole time we were married. She's even staying with us now.
I can't live because it's so uncomfortable.
If it's so uncomfortable, move out! why aren't you moving out?
Does it make sense to share the living space when we're in this state?
Why would I move out? YOU MOVE OUT! To your mother's whom you love so much.
Is this a contest to see who could yell louder?
It's court!
Do you think men cheat for no reason? That doesn't mean I have cheated.
You said there is nothing going on between you and the racing girl.
If there is nothing going on, and you slept with her. What kind of relationship is that?
What's going on? Why do you have to meet my older sister?
-Stay by my side.
-I know, of course I will stay by your side.
-You're here?
-Hello.
Take a seat. Hurry and get to the point.
-I want to date her
-I said no motorcycle
-I sold it.
-No way.
How can I trust that?
I thought you wouldn't believe me, so I the proof here with me.
[transferred from Yewon Motors, sales of used good]
I think you're quite young. Your eyesight haven't diminished due to age. You could read it right away.
I feel like you're trying to kiss up to me. Your kissing up is getting on my nerves.
Please be more understanding. Not everyone is used to the way he speaks.
Your motorcycle was expensive. That was used, still cost quite a bit.
Motorcycles usually don't drop in prices as much as automobiles.
A lot of people are into vintage motorcycles so used one could cost even more than a new one. It could also be a good investment.
-Did you sell yours?
-Not yet.
He sold his, why can't you sell yours?
-Are you going to hit her?
-No, I just wanted to scare her.
Then she's all yours.
I will ask him to sell mine as well.
-You must really like Deulrae.
-Deulrae chase after me soo much. So I am dating her.
What?
This is the way how he speaks.
-He means he really very likes me
-Yes
You're quite something.
I am quite something since something is my face. I am quite good looking you know.
Anyway, seeing how you brought proof since you predicted that I won't believe you. It seems like you won't go hungry.
-Did I pass?
-You've passed
I am a widow. Do you have to be like this in front of a widow?
Even flowers could bloom during winter. I guess you're the flower that blooms in the winter(at old age)
Winter is too much. It's autumn at my age.
-Anyway, give dating a serious chance
-I don't want to
Why not? You've just asked my permission to date her
-I want to marry her.
-Why get married?
Good. Get married.
Are you giving my hand in marriage a little too easily?
If a guy wants to live with you when your're 50 years old, you say hooray and live with him.
You're the best!
I will stay over at Hyejin's place today. You two take care of yourselves.
Is it okay if we do nothing?
If we do nothing like the last time, your sister wouldn't like that.
Geez. How old are you two?
-43 years old.
-50 years old.
You are a match made in heaven. Both are idiots.
Bye.
Plaintiff Mr. Nam Dohyun. Do you currently have any complaints about how Mrs. Jung Hyejin is raising Nam Taewon?
I do have hope that he could be brought up with more independence
You are insisting on custody of the child. How do you plan to raise the child?
I will have a professional nanny.
Where would he live?
You are currently living with Mrs. Jung Hyejin.
I plan on getting a house that I will live with my son
You need to have a specific environment prepared. You're being too abstract
How and where do you plan to hire a professional nanny?
After the divorce is finalized, I plan to sell the house and move into a small condo near my mother's
Since the child is still young, I plan to focus and raising him instead of getting a job right away.
Plaintiff Mr. Nam Dohyun and Defendant Mrs. Jung Hyejin is unable to come to agreement on custody of the child,
On the next meeting, in order to decide who should have the custody of the child.
I will look into your son's state of mind when he is with either one of you.
Do you have something to add?
Are we really getting married? Why did you decided it by yourself without even consulting me?
-So you don't like it?
-No, I like it
My first marriage, I got married because everyone else was getting married.
Second marriage, I was on a rebound from my first marriage.
I am happy when I am with you.
I am happy when I am with you too. So I want to live with you.
But you shouldn't have sold your motorcycle. I don't want that kind of sacrifice.
I was much more calculating when I was younger. When I was dating a girl, I thought this a plus and this is a minus.
But my calculations were always wrong.
A woman I date shouldn't be calculated.
I think that was the reason why I failed in both of my marriages.
Maybe you didn't like her enough. That's why you were calculating.
If you had really liked her, I don't think you'd have been calculating numbers.
I guess you want to hear I only really like you.
Yes
-I think I liked them all when I married them
-Get out.
-I was about to leave. I have to be somewhere.
-Where do you have to be?
-A welcome party for a divorcee.
"A beast living inside me". You use that quite well.
That's what you said. You should apply for a trademark. The men who cheat for no reason will like that.
I can't give you the custody of child.
If I had wanted you to decide on that matter, I wouldn't have met you in court.
You cannot raise a child with your will and desire only.
I don't think the judge was impressed by you today.
I think we are on equal footing now.
It's too early to celebrate. After the investigation is over, it will move to arbitration.
I really didn't want to hate you this much.
Whenever I see you, every fiber of my being is on the edge.
We had a chance to not become like this.
You threw it away.
You're blaming me? Who asked for the divorce?
Same thing all the time. Why don't you understand that the first one to ask for divorce is the one who's been more patient and tried harder.
You will make me hate even the memories of my loving you.
I wanted to keep them at least.
You're still far away. Far. Seriously.
seriously.
Did you mess it up today as well?
No, not that bad. I will do better next time.
-It shouldn't be "not that bad". You have to do well.
-I know. I will do well next time for sure.
The judge seems to have shifted after learning Dohyun has cheated.
That's a relief. Deulrae is getting married.
with whom? Minho?
They are head over heels for each other. I guess everyone has their soulmate out there.
That's quite a surprise. What does she like about him?
-Because he wants to marry Deulrae he even sold his motorcycle.
-Really?
Deulrae is quite blessed. He owns a building, some land
Even though he's divorced, he doesn't have any kids. He has what he needs to have and doesn't have what's unnecessary.
It's hard for it to be that way.
I am happy to hear a good news in a long time.
-I think it was me.
What was?
The reason Haeyoon broke up
No way. I am sure you're mistaken
No. If I put the pieces together, I think that's the case.
Sangjin said so too.
What if that's really the case?
No way mom.
If I hear that from my daughter, I think my life would be over.
Mom, you're being weak. That's not true.
Even the strong ones, it's different with their children.
You're right. It's not the same with your kids.
I am afraid Taewon will blame me when he grows up or think that I took his dad away from him
This is the reason the parent is always on the losing side to their kids.
Kids make you think all ridiculous notions.
Then why do you have ridiculous thoughts as these? Why do you think you are a hindrance to us?
Shouldn't your name be on the Guinness records?
as the shortest marriage ever?
Britney Spears' marriage lasted 55 hours. He beat her.
-I wasn't counting
-Anyway, congrats on being single again.
I will get divorced soon. All of us are single now then.
-We should party hard one of these day
-Count me out
-With the aunt?
-It turned out that way.
You had to do that. Why get married? Just have fun with her.
Congratulations for not stopping at having fun but getting married
Thank you.
You hold a grudge.
Because I gave you some advice before, you kept that in your mind.
Why are you picking a fight this kid?
I am not a kid. From now on, don't ask me to hang out if Dohyun will be there.
This cute guy. He clearly expresses what he wants.
I don't dislike you. We almost became a family.
I don't have anything against my sister-in-law.
Come to think of it, I almost became a family to you as well Minho.
Please don't drink too much today. I don't want to listen to your drunken tirades.
You're cute. Pour me a glass.
I don't wan to.
I will pour you a glass.
Let's not go home tonight. None of you. We'll stay up here tonight.
-This poor fellow
-What, me?
yes, you. If you want to hold onto Hyejin, just go home.
Don't act out like someone who's seeking attention. Stop it.
I thought you'd know how I would feel.
Looking at how things are panning out, it won't end pleasantly
Let the old farts hang out together and let's step out.
where are you going?
you look well.
I am doing well. Chae Young isn't bad.
I think she's quite something. It would be hard to act like that after being born into that kind of family.
Seeing someone like her, I think nutcases like her change the world for sure.
The favor you asked before. Banking account under an alias. You took your money out because you didn't want to give money to Haejin?
For surgeons, there is a period when you have the golden touch.
I am at my prime now. I know it.
How long do you think I will be able to perform surgery? Do you know how many plastic surgery clinics are there in Gangam alone?
Many more are popping out and in order to survive, I have to continually upgrade my clinic.
Just because things are going well now, there's no guarantee it will all go well later.
I saw many cases when people are ruined with just one mistake.
Asking me to give her half of my assets, that's too much.
I have to survive as well. Haejin doesn't understand how anxious I feel.
I am telling you this because it seems like you don't know what you want.
From what I could see, you seem to want to continue living with Hyejin.
She doesn't want to live with me. She told me fiber of her beings hate me.
Go beg for her forgiveness. In the end, she's bound to give in.
As you continue living with her, fiber of her beings will familiarize themselves to you again.
Do you think it will really work if I beg her?
I guess you don't have to be home tonight.
Do you like me this much?
Mr. Gong Gijoong. It's no fun if you're so easy to predict.
What's so easy to predict?
Why do you come looking for your ex after being divorced?
Are you sure your venture will succeed with such a predictable imagination of yours?
It's cold outside.
I hope it's winter break soon.
-There are not many days left.
-I know.
I haven't washed up. Hurry and wash up first.
-How come you haven't washed up yet?
-I was just laying around
You're here.
Older sis, can you lend me your cleansing cream? I didn't bring anything with me.
Okay.
-Here
-Thank you.
What did you say to Attorney Jung?
What do you mean?
Earlier mom said that Attorney Jung told her that you two broke up because of mom.
I told you to make sure mom wouldn't find out.
You know he's quite smart. I guess that's the conclusion he drew.
Why are you talking as if we're talking about someone else?
Like I told you before, you should have been more careful.
Do I have stop his thoughts?
Even he thinks mom's not being sensible.
you were always like this
when all of us were fighting difficult everyday called life, you built your room and stayed there.
emotional luxury that you enjoy in your room is possible because the mom you criticize fought against the world to make it happen.
Do you know the despair I felt when I gave up on going to college?
I could have gone to college too if I insisted. But I thought of you.
Because if I take a lot, your share decreases.
I thought you were more qualified since you got better grades.
You chose that path. I don't want you to blame me.
I am not blaming you.
When we gave up a little of ours as a family. I am asking what did you give up?
How is it fair that you criticize mom for not being sensible?
Why are you getting worked up over nothing, bringing up past and all?
I am afraid my kid will think like you after I try my best to raise him.
I can you judge your parent under the name of common sense?
If you were going to to do that, you shouldn't have enjoyed the privileges mom gave you.
What kind of privilege did I enjoy?
I worked part time during college and contributed to this household as well.
Working part time for your tuition, is that for the household? That's for yourself.
It's not like you were able to earn full amount of your tuition. You used your pay as your spending money.
What you just said right now, goes against the "common sense" you talk about.
Everyone starts judging parents objectively once they reach puberty.
I am not the odd one out, it's you who stand out.
That's why you were pushed by mom into a wrong marriage.
What? A wrong marriage?
It is a wrong marriage